

#### **P**ROFILE

Zhipeng yu 1990.9.5 +86 17769712562 China / Chinese citizen x315043655@outlook.com zhejiang construction tech school major:construction field engineering

Great communication skills with a colorful and Positive personality which was built by my Rich experience.

Tough and reliable, capable in many scenario, in detail you can find me never late for work, can handle things and get the job done, get my people covered, work hard

Physically hard to get sick or Injured, Quick reaction, Quick recovery from damage, both eyesight are at 5.2~5.3.

#### WEBSITE:

https://www.youtube.com/channel/UC8aj 3Xp8DbDLqCjYg3C3ERQ

#### HOBBIES

Cat
Travel by motorcycles
Adventure
Ruins adventure
Apocalypse scenario,
like zombie apocalypse
Photography
Outdoor camping and cooking
Video game squad/war thunder
Favorite place: Thailand

# Max Yu

my portfolio https://dinnexbell.github.io/resume-beyond/generic.html

# Current career background and future plans

# IT support /network engineer

Good at English(native), Japanese and Chinese(native).

rapid response and learning ability.

A fast learner with powerful logical thinking.

Communication skills , Empathy for my customers, Understand how they feel

Efficient skill on investigation, troubleshooting & breaking fixes.

passion and ability to maintain a complex system in optimal condition, happen to see things running fast and fluid.

Take advantage of big tech , build my own vps server with load balancing feature on Azure and Google cloud ,have more ideas, love network technology ,good with tcp/ip udp optimization.

Pretty good with centos/Ubuntu technology, HTML CSS JavaScript

Python general, automation with selenium.

Rich knowledge about mainstream products and cyber security

Familiarity with OS Internals concepts (Windows, Linux, etc.), Storage, AD and Security.

Deep understanding of underlying logic on Windows, concepts and system administration.

Happy to use cloud services, good with configuration and administration.

Familiarity with networking tools/protocols (tcp/ip, http, ping, tracert, tracemon, wire shark, etc.)

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

## HCL, shanghai- tech support for huntsman

2020 - 2020

Primary Job

Manage Equipment warehouse and AD , quick response to VIP customers, support all staff of Windows 10 devices, Software. and Hardware , printers, conference rooms and daily situation reports.

Troubleshoot and solve all software-level problems, Set VPN,

Disassemble and troubleshoot problems, Identify faulty hardware and request replacement with the service provider.

Answer various questions of users

Because the house I rented was newly painted and the formaldehyde exceeded the standard, I had a sudden health problem. It looked very serious at that time, so I left my job

## Wicresoft/Microsoft, shanghai—support engineer

2018 - 2019

As part of the outsource support team, helping customers solve problems on MS products.

Primarily in Windows 10, And win server pre-sales

Help customers solve problems by phone, email, remote control, etc., and then send a request for evaluation

Windows 10 has a variety of problems, but most of them are easy to fix , and so is the pre-sales part of winserver, most of the time, it only takes 2-3 steps , reset some services, PowerShell, modify the registry and redirect some functions to solve the problem.

This is my first IT job, so I entered this industry. I want to thank wicresoft.

# zhejiang shengheng international, overseas Overseas sales

2015 - 2017

Because Zhejiang's foreign trade business was very advanced, we have a lot of small factories.

One of my local friends is a factory owner, we call them small boss (小老板), He is short of people in Africa, so I worked for him.

One of our major markets is in Kano State, Nigeria.

The locals are black Muslim, Hausa people, very good honest people, like if you drop 1000 usd on the ground for a day, its still there, they will not take for themselves.

Hausa people like brightly colorful fabrics, like the red, which must be big bright red, as red as the apple Snow White ate.

This requires a technique called 蜡染,wax printing, our factory is good at this.

There are huge markets in Kano, with tens of thousands of shops, and ours is one of them, because everyone are lazy, we go to work at noon and leave work at 5:00 pm

The afternoon became busy, vendors pushing carts full of food and small goods, we walked in the market, visit other shops and discussed styles in popular fabrics.

### **Zhejiang Jincheng Trade Co., Ltd,** shaoxing -European line sales

2013 - 2015

The main work is to maintain communication with customers, understand customers' needs, and find new customers at the fair.

When customers come to the factory and show them around, it's a service-oriented job.

#### **EDUCATION**

## zhejiang construction technology school, college

#### hangzhou — Construction engineer

September 2009 September-September 2013 September

Mainly study architectural engineering

We need to learn building budget, building mechanics, building construction, drawing 2D and 3D architectural blueprints, and looking for mistakes in design.

I have high talent in three-dimensional graphics, my CAD drawing is very powerful, and my architectural mechanics is also very powerful

I began to realize that the development of the world is promoted by science, science, engineering and technology. They built the world.

# zhejiang construction technology school , high school

## shaoxing—Construction engineer

September 2006 September-September 2009 September

Complete architecture is taught from high school, university will teach more advanced architectural mechanics and architectural CAD drawing, architectural budget